

# Erkan Bostan

.Net Developer

rkanbstn34@gmail.com 🤰 0 536 321 72 19 👂 Avcılar / İstanbul

## **Profile**

I graduated from Balıkesir University Computer Programming Department in 2022.

While I was studying, I also took part in Zesu Socks as a Full-Stack developer for 3 years.

After graduation, I took part in CODEX as a Full Stack developer, mostly .Net Core and React technologies.

I am currently actively developing using .NET and ANGULAR Technologies.

I have worked with many institutions such as Genç Yalvaçlılar Social Assistance Institution, Yaren and Şifa Pharmacy, La P'tite Fringe Restaurant on a Project Basis and I am still continuing my freelance career.

You can review my Repository on my Github account to have information about all the projects and technologies I use. Thanks for your time.

# **Employment**

#### **Software Developer**

May 2023 - Present

PEAKUP Technologies, İstanbul

I work as a Software Developer for the analysis and coding of new projects using technologies such as .Net Core and Angular the software of existing projects, the provision of necessary revisions and product development within the company.

### Software Developer

Oct 2022 - Feb 2023

CODEX, İstanbul

I worked as a Software Specialist in the analysis and coding of new projects using technologies such as .Net Core, Flutter and React, the software of existing projects, the necessary revisions within the company and product development.

#### Software Developer

Jul 2019 - Aug 2021

Zesu Socks, İstanbul

As a Software Developer at the company, I took part in usercentered digital/program design and development in software solutions and information processing.

#### Software Developer

Dec 2019 - Present

Freelancer, İstanbul

I develop projects/systems such as enterprise, B2B, E-Commercial web systems and desktop automation programs suitable for software architectures with OOP programming experience.

## Personal details

Date of birth July 12, 2001

Driver's license

Website

erkanbostan.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/erkanbostan

Github

github.com/erkanbstn

Bionluk

bionluk.com/devxgeo

Military Service Delayed

# Languages

English - Reading

English - Writing

English - Speaking

# My Interest

.Net Core Identity Redis-Cache Docker RabbitMQ MicroService **SOLID Pattern** Unit Of Work SignalR

Unit Test

### Education

#### **Computer Programming**

Sep 2020 - Jul 2022

Balıkesir University, Balıkesir

I graduated from Balıkesir University Computer Programming Department.

# Internships

#### Software Development

Jan 2021 - Jul 2021

Ecodation Company, İstanbul

I Completed My Internship by Completing Project Creation and Development, Interface Design and Back-End Coding and OOP Trainings

#### Web Development

Jul 2021 - Jul 2021

Istanbul Business Institute, İstanbul

I Completed My Internship Training Based On Creating And Developing Projects With Asp.Net MVC and Web Forms Templates.

# Certificates

C# Programmer

Jul 2021

The C# Programming Certificate I Obtained After the Training I Completed and the Project Tests I Passed at YTU Teknopark/Ecodation Company

#### .NET Programmer

Sep 2021

.Net Programming Certificate I Obtained After Project Tests I Completed on Istanbul Business Institute.

### References

Recep Firat - Software Team Leader

RF Software Solution, istanbul

0541 439 21 62, recep@softwaresolution.com

Furkan Bostanoğlu - Software Team Leader

Artware Software, İstanbul

0507 201 24 28, furkanbostanoglu@artware.com.tr

Hakan Şimşek - Software Team Leader

Polinity Group, İstanbul

0507 632 77 05, hakansimsek7485@gmail.com

# Skills

.Net Core 5.0, 6.0, 7.0

.Net Framework 4.8

Asp.Net Core MVC

Asp.Net Web Forms

**Entity Framework Core** 

**RESTFUL API** 

JavaScript

**TypeScript** 

**Angular** 

Windows Form Application

DevExpress Tools and Components

MS SQL Server / T-SQL

PostgreSQL

PL/SQL (Oracle)